Finding Aid for the Jason Brown Collection
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
Jason Brown Collection
undated
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
MSS.0833
Biographical Sketch
Jason Brown was born in England. He currently works as an art collector and a curator of original art exhibitions, including Cab Gallery, Reinvention: A Mail Art Project, and most recently Letter to Me: A Mail Art Project. Beginning in 1999, Brown and London art dealer Paul Stolper worked together to curate Cab Gallery. The two brought in worldwide talent by sending artists the taxi’s dimensions and space—usually available for advertising—which would hold the artists’ inspired works of art. Brown, a cab driver in London during the three-year exhibition period, agreed not to acknowledge the art to riders--who became patrons upon entering the cab--but freely provided information if someone took interest. Brown later moved to Nashville, Tennessee in 2012. In February 2014, inspired by his relocation, Brown began his next project, Reinvention: A Mail Art Project. Brown agreed to donate the collection to Vanderbilt Special Collections after the finish of the exhibition. His newest project, Letter to Me: A Mail Art Project, accepted works from January until July 1 of 2015, and those works are arranged in boxes 19 – 22 of this collection.
Scope & Content Note
The collection of works came first from a call to participate in a Mail Art project “Reinvention.” The curator, Jason Brown, asked for works on a global and local scale with the theme of “Reinvention.” Brown’s project outline stated that his blog would display the received mail art, which the works would eventually go on exhibition in Nashville, Tennessee, and it gave no inhibitions. The technique of art was “free,” meaning, not limited to any media and the size was “free,” expressing no limitations on what could be mailed. Moreover, there would be no jury selection, no mail art returned, and no sales of the objects sent. Brown cataloged the pieces, the project outline, news releases and other documentation of the project, and its exhibition history on his blog:
The call for mail art was in February 2014 and the 460 pieces from 31 countries were received until mid-August of that year. The scope of the project is quite limited then, between February and August 2014.
The contents are extremely varied due to the “free” project guidelines. The pieces are all considered Mail Art, but otherwise they are made of different material, reused objects, and other miscellaneous forms. The curator organized the documents in the order he received them, grouping them into “pages.” He published the entire series in these pages on his blog. The Vanderbilt Special Collections housing will keep the integrity of the series order, but will sort them by box order rather than “page” groupings. The website’s documentation of the pieces designates what is considered the piece of art with parenthetical descriptions after the artist’s name or other pertinent information. In order to match this online catalog, the artist’s name, any parenthetical citations, and the artist’s location are included in the container list. Any oversize material is denoted in the original order by an “oversize” page. The oversize boxes keep the original order of the pieces within each box, but the boxes themselves are sorted by size rather than content.
The second mail art project “Letter to Me” was donated to Special Collections in August 2015, and the inclusive dates for this second mail art project were January 20, 2015 – July 1, 2015.
This project features the letters of approximately 200 participants from 26 countries, and several languages are represented.
Brown encouraged the participants to use present, past and future tenses for their art letters.
Provenance Note
Jason Brown, the curator of the exhibition, Reinvention: A Mail Art Project, donated the collection in its entirety to Vanderbilt University Special Collections in the fall of 2014. He donated the second mail art project Letter to Me: A Mail Art Project in its entirety to VU Special Collections in August 2015.
- “Reinvention” Mail Art Project
  - Andee Rudloff - Kentucky, USA (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Andre Pace (Inserts) - Arizona, USA (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Coorain Devin - Massachusetts, USA (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Jaromir Svozilik (Insert) - Norway (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Michel Della Vedova - France (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Russell Manning (Insert) - Texas, USA (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Vittore Baroni (Envelope & Inserts) - Italy (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - David Stanley Aponte (Sub-Real Alchemy) - Indiana, USA (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Stephanie Blake (Outside & Inside) - Alabama, USA (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - John Held, Jr. (Envelope & Inserts) - California, USA (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Valentine Mark Herman ‘Turning the Wheels’ - France (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Joel ‘The Sticker Dude’ Cohen (Envelope-Front, -Back & Inserts) - New York, USA (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - W.C. “Bill” Porter (Front & Back) - Colorado, USA (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Jim Leftwich (Inserts) - Virginia, USA (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Gandha Key (Insert Front & Back) - England (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Pedro Bericat - Spain (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - John Bennett (Inserts) - Ohio, USA (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Bruno Chiarlone - Italy (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Diane Keys - Illinois, USA (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Sassu Antonio (Inserts) - Italy (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Otto D Sherman (Envelope-Front, -Back & Inserts) - New York, USA (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Fleur Helsingor - California, USA (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Andrew Maximillian Niss (Insert) - Germany (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Robert Askew (Envelope-Front & Inserts) - California, USA (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Anne L. Braunschweig - New Mexico, USA (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Claudio Grandinetti (Insert) - Italy (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Amanda Kinsman - England (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - R. F. Cote (Front & Back) - Canada (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Tiziana Baracchi (Envelope & Inserts) - Italy (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Norbert Koczorski (Envelope & Insert) - Germany (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Indiana Rogers (Envelope-Front, -Back & Insert Title: Baby Can’t Be Broken) - California, USA (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Note from Kelly Copas - Warren Regional Juvenile Detention Center, Bowling Green, (WRJDC) Kentucky, USA (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - M.B. - WRJDC, Kentucky, USA (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Unknown - WRJDC, Kentucky, USA (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Unknown - WRJDC, Kentucky, USA (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - B.W. - WRJDC, Kentucky, USA (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Unknown - WRJDC, Kentucky, USA (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - W.M. - WRJDC, Kentucky, USA (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - A.L. - WRJDC, Kentucky, USA (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - T.M. - WRJDC, Kentucky, USA (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Unknown - WRJDC, Kentucky, USA (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - A.T.B. - WRJDC, Kentucky, USA (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Unknown - WRJDC, Kentucky, USA (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - K.L.W. - WRJDC, Kentucky, USA (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - M.B. - WRJDC, Kentucky, USA (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Unknown - WRJDC, Kentucky, USA (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Unknown - WRJDC, Kentucky, USA (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - Unknown - WRJDC, Kentucky, USA (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - C.S. - WRJDC, Kentucky, USA (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - C.S. - WRJDC, Kentucky, USA (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - Unknown - WRJDC, Kentucky, USA (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - Unknown - WRJDC, Kentucky, USA (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - K.T.B. - WRJDC, Kentucky, USA (Box 1, Folder 53)
  - Unknown - WRJDC, Kentucky, USA (Box 1, Folder 54)
  - Unknown - WRJDC, Kentucky, USA (Box 1, Folder 55)
  - T.M. - WRJDC, Kentucky, USA (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Unknown - WRJDC, Kentucky, USA (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Unknown - WRJDC, Kentucky, USA (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Unknown - WRJDC, Kentucky, USA (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Unknown - WRJDC, Kentucky, USA (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - T.M. - WRJDC, Kentucky, USA (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - T.M. - WRJDC, Kentucky, USA (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - M.B. - WRJDC, Kentucky, USA (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - J.H. - WRJDC, Kentucky, USA (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - B.D.T. - WRJDC, Kentucky, USA (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - K.B. - WRJDC, Kentucky, USA (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - M.B. - WRJDC, Kentucky, USA (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - B.W. - WRJDC, Kentucky, USA (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - T.A. - WRJDC, Kentucky, USA (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - M.T. - WRJDC, Kentucky, USA (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - M.B. - WRJDC, Kentucky, USA (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - B.L.M. - WRJDC, Kentucky, USA (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Giovanni and Renata straDA DA (Envelope-Front, -Back, & Inserts) - Italy (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Seth McInteer (Front, Back, & Insert - Broken) - Tennessee, USA - oversize (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Robert Ridley-Shackleton (Insert) - England (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - OBVIOUSFRONT (Front & Back) - Illinois, USA (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - EVER ARTS (Insert) - The Netherlands (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Michael Thompson (Envelope & Insert) - Illinois, USA (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Lunar Suede (Inserts) - Canada (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Jurgen Volkert-Marten - Germany (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Jean-Pierre Comes - France (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Carol Stetser (Envelope-Front & Inserts) - Arizona, USA (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Connie Jean (Front & Back) - Florida, USA (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Pietro Romano Matarrese (Insert - lemon juice on paper) - Italy (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Costas Evangelatos (Insert) - Greece (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Otto D Sherman (Envelope & Insert) - New York, USA (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Reed Altemus (Envelope-Front & Inserts) - Maine, USA (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Emilio Morandi (Insert) - Italy (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Roberto Scala (Inserts) - Italy (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Duncan MacAskill (Front & Back) - France (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Peter W. Kaufmann (Envelope & Insert) - Switzerland (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Wolfgang Kraus - aka Welfchen (Front & Back) - Germany (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Joel ‘The Sticker Dude’ Cohen (Envelope & Inserts) - New York, USA (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Gloria G. Persiani (Insert) - Italy (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Miche-Art-Universalis (Envelope & Insert) - Belgium (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Igor Jovanovie (Insert) - Serbia - oversize (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Darlene Atlschul DKA POST (Envelope & Insert) - California, USA (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Johan Van Geluwe (Envelope-Front, -Back, & Inserts) - Belgium (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Michael Courtois - France (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - Pascal Lenoir (Envelope & Insert) - France (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - Chris James (Insert) - Australia (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - Bethany Lee ‘The Question’ (Front & Back) - Florida, USA (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - Darlene Altschul DKA Post (Inserts) - California, USA (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - Silvano Pertone ‘PSYCHE OUT Fanzine’ (Envelope & Insert) - Italy (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - Bernhard Zilling (Front & Back) - Germany (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - Otto D Sherman (Front, Back, & Inside) - New York, USA (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - Lawrence Weiner (Front & Back) - Arizona, USA (Box 2, Folder 52)
  - Raz Mail Art (Front & Back) - Australia (Box 2, Folder 53)
  - Mars Tokyo (Front & Back) - Maryland, USA (Box 2, Folder 54)
  - Jennifer A. Weigel - Missouri, USA - oversize (Box 2, Folder 55)
  - Duncan MacAskill (Front & Back) - California, USA (Box 2, Folder 56)
  - Eni Ilis (Envelope-Front, -Back, & Insert) - Brazil (Box 2, Folder 57)
  - Miguel Jimenez (Front & Back) - Spain (Box 2, Folder 58)
  - Michael Wagner - Germany (Box 2, Folder 59)
  - Paul Tiililä (Front & Back) - Finland (Box 2, Folder 60)
  - Juan Lopez de Ael (Front & Back) - Spain (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Duncan MacAskill (Front & Back) - England (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Schoko Casana Rosso - Germany (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Moan Lisa (Envelope & Insert) - Iowa, USA (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Keiichi Nakamura - Japan (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Michael Wagner - Germany (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - BamBamArt - England (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Judy Skolnick - District of Columbia, USA (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Stephen Stephenson (Front & Back) - England (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Duncan MacAskill (Front & Back) - England (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Michael Wagner - Germany (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Lancillotto Bellini (Envelope-Front, -Back, & Insert-Book) - Italy (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Anacanela (Front & Back) - Belgium (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Otto D Sherman (Envelope & Inserts) - New York, USA (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Shauna Richardson (Top View & Under View) - England - oversize (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Duncan MacAskill (Front & Back) - Spain (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Matthew Rose (Front & Back) - France (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Michael Wagner - Germany (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Otto D Sherman (Envelope-Front, -Back, & Inserts) - New York, USA (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Susie Hamilton ‘Supermarket 1’ & ‘Supermarket 2’ - England (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Piet Franzen/SIDAC (Front & Back) - The Netherlands (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Cheryl Penn (Envelope, ‘Bhubezi Mythology’ Insert, & Insert) - South Africa (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Duncan MacAskill (Front & Back) - Scotland (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Shannon (Front & Back) - Canada (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Michele Courtois - France (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Lucy (Envelope & Insert) - California, USA (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Daniel de Culla (Inserts) - Spain (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Torma Cauli (Envelope-Front & Insert) - Hungary (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Duncan MacAskill (Front & Back) - Wales (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Ko De Jonge (Front & Back) - The Netherlands (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Alice Stallard - England (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - rod summers/vec ‘Gift of the Sparrow’ (Front & Back) - The Netherlands (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Clemente Padin (Front & Back) - Uruguay (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Alan Turner (Front & Back) - Wales (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Katerina Nikoltsou ‘Reinvent Time’ (Envelope-Front, -Back & Insert-Front, -Back) - Greece (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Jose Luis Alcalde Soberanes - Mexico (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - Snappy (Envelope-Front, & Insert-Front, -Back) - Canada (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - Duncan MacAskill (Front & Back) - Japan (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - Ptrzia(TICTAC) (Envelope-Front, Insert-Front, -Back, & Inserts) - Germany (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - Jurgen O Olbrich ‘? of the world is missing !’ (Envelope-Front & Inserts) - Germany (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - Reid Wood (Front & Back) - Ohio, USA (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - MerriYum (Front & Back) - Tennessee, USA (Box 3, Folder 42)
  - Sheridan Seward - BFA Student - State University, New York, USA (Box 3, Folder 43)
  - Jennifer Varvaro - BFA Student - State University, New York, USA (Box 3, Folder 44)
  - Mark Linkletter - BFA Student - State University, New York, USA (Box 3, Folder 45)
  - Jean-Phillip Narcisse - BFA Student - State University, New York, USA (Box 3, Folder 46)
  - Sarah Frizalone - BFA Student - State University, New York, USA (Box 3, Folder 47)
  - Melissa Digiovanna - BFA Student - State University, New York, USA (Box 3, Folder 48)
  - Tyler Verderame - BFA Student - State University, New York, USA (Box 3, Folder 49)
  - Messina Brianna - BFA Student - State University, New York, USA (Box 3, Folder 50)
  - Chelsea Burgett - BFA Student - State University, New York, USA (Box 3, Folder 51)
  - Rebecca Smith - BFA Student - State University, New York, USA (Box 3, Folder 52)
  - Shanika Scarborough - BFA Student - State University, New York, USA (Box 3, Folder 53)
  - Hunter Pettingill - BFA Student - State University, New York, USA (Box 3, Folder 54)
  - Brittany Koch - BFA Student - State University, New York, USA (Box 3, Folder 55)
  - Jessica Peters - BFA Student - State University, New York, USA (Box 3, Folder 56)
  - Sheridan Seward - BFA Student - State University, New York, USA (Box 3, Folder 57)
  - Desirae Collins - BFA Student - State University, New York, USA (Box 3, Folder 58)
  - Jennifer Varvaro - BFA Student - State University, New York, USA (Box 3, Folder 59)
  - Meaghan Quinn - BFA Student - State University, New York, USA (Box 3, Folder 60)
  - Messina Brianna - BFA Student - State University, New York, USA (Box 3, Folder 61)
  - Shanika Scarborough - BFA Student - State University, New York, USA (Box 3, Folder 62)
  - Rebecca Smith - BFA Student - State University, New York, USA (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Melissa Digiovanna - BFA Student - State University, New York, USA (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Mark Linkletter - BFA Student - State University, New York, USA (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Tyler Verderame - BFA Student - State University, New York, USA (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Joel Dodge - BFA Student - State University, New York, USA (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Donovan King - BFA Student - State University, New York, USA (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Jessica Delgadillo - BFA Student - State University, New York, USA (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Jessica Peters - BFA Student - State University, New York, USA (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Brittany Koch- BFA Student - State University, New York, USA (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Hunter Pettingill - BFA Student - State University, New York, USA (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Meaghan Quinn - BFA Student - State University, New York, USA (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Jessica Voorsanger (Front & Back) - England (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Dorian Ribas Marinho (Inserts) - Brazil (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Bee Greschak - New York, USA (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Duncan MacAskill (Front & Back) - The Aran Islands, Ireland (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Liisa Soini (Front & Back) - Finland (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Lydia Denkler ‘Images from my travels. Marfa, Texas’ - Tennessee, USA (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Carlo Maria Giudici (Envelope-Front & Inside) - Italy (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Kevin & James Gillen - England (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - IBIRICO - Spain (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - 21. Johan Van Geluwe (Envelope-Front, -Back, & Inserts) - Belgium - missing the envelope & some inserts (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - D Siemers-Wulff (Front & Back) - Germany (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Carlyle Baker (Envelope & Inserts) - Canada (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Clemente Padin (Front & Back) - Uruguay (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Ed Giecek (Envelope-Front, -Back, & Inserts) - Washington, USA (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Duncan MacAskill (Front & Back) - The Netherlands (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Dorian Ribas Marinho (Inserts) - Brazil (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Cristina Blank (Envelope & Insert) - Germany (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Stephen Farthing RA (Front & Back) - England (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Wendy Whittemore (Front & Back) - Tennessee, USA (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Duncan MacAskill (Front & Back) - The Isle of Arran, Scotland (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Jose Roberto Sechi (Envelope-Front & Inserts) - Brazil (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Susie Hamilton (Front & Back) - Morocco (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - GX Jupitter-Larsen (Front & Back) - California, USA (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - Pier Roberto Bassi (Front, Back, & Attached) - Italy (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - Mark Pawson (Front & Back) - England (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - BOEK 861 (Envelope-Front), Isabel Jover (Insert), Cesar Reglero, & (Inserts) - Spain (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - Mike Prater LO-FI (Front & Back) - Tennessee, USA (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - Ryosuke Cohen (Envelope-Front & Inserts) - Japan (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - Wheeling Ice - North Carolina, USA (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - Kurt Beaulieu (Envelope-Front & Inserts) - Canada (Box 4, Folder 41)
  - Duncan MacAskill (Front & Back) - Ireland (Box 4, Folder 42)
  - Kaaren Hirschowitz Engel (Front & Back) - Tennessee, USA (Box 4, Folder 43)
  - Duncan MacAskill (Front & Back) - France (Box 4, Folder 44)
  - Donald Smith ‘Colour Space 2014’ (Front & Back) - England - oversize (Box 4, Folder 45)
  - LuAnn T Palazzo ‘The Design Diva’ (Envelope-Back & Inserts) - New York, USA (Box 4, Folder 46)
  - Lutz Beeke (Front & Back) - Germany (Box 4, Folder 47)
  - Anja Mattila-Tolvanen (Envelope-Front & Artist Book) - Finland (Box 4, Folder 48)
  - Susanne Tierney - Florida, USA (Box 4, Folder 49)
  - Simonson (Envelope-Front & Insert) - Washington, USA (Box 4, Folder 50)
  - Elisa Battistella (Envelope-Front & Insert) - Italy - oversize (Box 4, Folder 51)
  - Duncan MacAskill (Front & Back) - Switzerland (Box 4, Folder 52)
  - Mark Sonnenfeld Marymark Press (Artist Book) - New Jersey, USA (Box 4, Folder 53)
  - Luc Fierens (Front & Back) - Belgium (Box 4, Folder 54)
  - Unknown (Envelope-Front & Inserts) - USA (Box 4, Folder 55)
  - Ryosuke Cohen (Envelope-Front & Inserts) - Japan (Box 4, Folder 56)
  - Jon Smith ‘POP GUN’ (Front & Back) - The Netherlands - oversize (Box 4, Folder 57)
  - Susan Forsyth (Package) & Sculpture ‘Mignon 2014’ - England - oversize (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Keith Bates (Envelope-Front, -Back, & Inserts) - England (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Duncan MacAskill (Front & Back) - The Netherlands (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Kay Ramming - Tennessee, USA (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Guy Bleus The Administration Centre (Envelope-Front, -Back & Insert-Front, -Back) - Belgium (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Jeff Prant (3 x Postcards-Front, 3 x Postcards-Back) - New York, USA (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - M Elliot - Tennessee, USA (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Daniel DALIGAND (Envelope-Front & Insert) - France (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Monica Rex ‘Ray of Light - Ray Johnson’ - California, USA (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Jurgen O Olbrich (Envelope-Front, Two Artist Books, & Postcard ‘Rainbow Objects Mandala-Floor Piece’) - Germany (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Henning Mittendorf (Envelope-Front, -Back, & Insert) - Germany (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Duncan MacAskill (Front & Back) - Switzerland (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Herve Alexandre - France (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Jeff Prant (3 x Postcards-Front & -Back) - New York, USA (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Ned Luberecki (Front & Back) - Tennessee, USA - oversize (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Serse Luigetti (Envelope-Front, -Back, & Inserts) - Italy (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Platetone (Front & Back) - Tennessee, USA (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Duncan MacAskill (Front & Back) - England (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - MerriYum (Front & Back) - Tennessee, USA (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Jeff Bertrand - Tennessee, USA (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Rosanna Veronesi (Envelope-Front, Insert-Front & -Back) - Italy (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Lain York (Insert) - Tennessee, USA (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Kaaren Hirschowitz Engel (Case-Front, -Back, & Inside) - Tennessee, USA (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Jeff Prant (2 x Postcards-Front & -Back) - New York, USA (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Robert Bruce Scott - Tennessee, USA (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Joan Crawford Hotdog (Envelope-Front & -Inside, Insert-Front & -Back) - California, USA (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Kevin Gillen - England (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - dadaimportexport ion(ilarion)isaila (Envelope-Front & Insert) - Germany (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Ed Barlow (Front & Back) - Tennessee, USA - oversize (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Sheila Wright (Front & Back) - Canada (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Duncan MacAskill (Front & Back) - Canada (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Pamela Butler ‘The Simple Life’ - Tennessee, USA (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - Kelly Kessler ‘Felix Baumgartner & Geoffrey Chaucer hang out in an Akkadian medium’ - Tennessee, USA - oversize (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - Obviousfront - Illinois, USA (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Kaaren Hirschowitz Engel - Tennessee, USA (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Mara Pauline (Envelope-Front, -Back, & Inserts) - California, USA (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Michael R Grine ‘Waffles’ - Tennessee, USA (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Keiichi Nakamura (Inserts) - Japan (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Private World / i.g.h (Envelope-Front & -Back, Inside, Inserts-Front & -Back) - Arizona, USA (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Marie Vailhe (Envelope-Front, -Back, & Insert) - France (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Rodni (Book-Front & -Back, Inside pages & stickers) - California, USA (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Richard Canard (Front & Back) - Illinois, USA (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Kelley Luberecki ‘At the Feeder’ (Front & Back) - Tennessee, USA - oversize (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Duncan MacAskill (Front & Back) - England (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Amy Gieske ‘...The Reinvention of the Polaroid’ (Front & Back) - Kentucky, USA (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Michael Iveson ‘Gammon Steaks’ (Insert) - England (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Hanna Bayer (Envelope-Front & Insert) - Germany (Box 6, Folder 14)